A Guide to the Papers of Alexander H. H. Stuart and the related Stuart and Baldwin families
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
C.W. Newton, one of the Commissioners chosen to select a site for the Norfolk Custom House, discusses the matter, and recommends that the other commissioners be retained as superintendents to continue with the construction of the Custom House (1851 May 1); asks why the delay in the appointment of his friend, Walter H. Taylor (1852 Aug 20); recommends John P. Leigh for the Postmaster position at Norfolk (1852 Sep 29)
Isaac C. Newton regrets his defence of Bryant who was removed from office by his own misconduct and not through prejudice as he claimed (1853 Jan 15)
Dr. C.N. Nichols concerning the purchase of " Woodstock, " the farm of Mrs. Brent and a note from John Carroll Brent (1852 Nov 23)
William Ogden Niles writes concerning the prosecution of parties arrested for frauds upon the Departments of the Interior and the Treasury (1850 Nov 12)
John A. North furnishes information in several cases in which Alexander H. H. Stuart is listed as Counsel in Judge Thompson's Circuit (1852 Aug 14)
John A. [Parker ?] thanks Alexander H. H. Stuart for his recent speech on the slavery question and Mr. Lincoln's plan to purchase land to colonize the freed Negroes (1873 Oct 27)
William Elisha Peters (1829-1906) urges Alexander H. H. Stuart through another faculty member not to use the revenue from the Corcoran fund for the general purposes of the University of Virginia or to any other than the benefit of the Professors which will assure the future of the institution (1876 Nov 23)
[Sir Flinders ?] Petrie, Secretary of the Victoria Institute or Philosophical Society of Great Britain, invites Alexander H. H. Stuart to join the society (1878 Aug 12)
Eb Phlegar furnishes a table of voting in the precincts of Montgomery County and Pulaski County (1841 Apr 24)
L.M. Powell expresses his concern over Alexander H. H. Stuart 's fall into the water and tells about the loss of his trunk (1860 Oct 23)
W.A. Powell statement of interest due (1868 Dec 16)
William Ballard Preston (1805-1862) discusses the Whig Convention in Philadelphia, the nomination of Zachary Taylor, the vulnerability of Lewis Cass, and mentions [John Minor] Botts (1848 Jun 15)
Charles Radziminski asks for a leave of absence to be arranged so he can travel to Europe and check on his family whom he has not heard from since his exile from Poland for revolutionary activity in 1834 (1852 Aug 1)
Robert Ridgway (1823-1870) asks Alexander H. H. Stuart if he would accept the opposition nomination for Governor and discusses others who might accept a position on the ticket (1859 Jan 9)
Lawrence Riggs writes about the desire of Rev. F.W. Hatch for the Chaplaincy to the U.S. Marine Hospital at St. Louis (1851 Jan 8)
Alexander Rives discusses the idea of secession, "A vague fear distresses us, lest our people should be maddened by occurrences at the South and dragged after the seceding states. I am clean for keeping the state out of that vortex." He also suggests that the Southern representatives meet with their Stephen Douglass allies and agree to serve in Lincoln's Cabinet if asked (1860 Nov 20) and "You can well conceive that I am not favorably inclined to our unceremonious & unexpected transfer to Jeff. Davis & Co. I did not like the Convention's adoption of Judge Allen's sophism in the preamble to the Act of Secession; -it is a false gloss and unworthy of the state;" (1861 May 13)
William Cabell Rives expresses hopes that they can create a great National Conservative Party to preserve the Union and avoid the extremism proclaimed by Mr. Seward in recent speeches in New York (1859 Jan 5); and fears his health will not permit him to give the speech on behalf of the Committee to the people of the United States; he died on April 25 (1868 Jan 7)
William Barton Rogers hesitates to endorse any mining and economical surveys, and mentions that he enjoyed the address of his friend Judge Bradley at the public exercises at the University of Virginia (1881 Jul 7)
W.H. Ruffner wishes that Alexander H. H. Stuart would receive the nomination for the Vice-Presidency and asks Alexander H. H. Stuart to come to Philadelphia to make a speech before the Convention, "A little glorification of Hungary -some leanings toward our `Manifest Destiny' -a few digs at `European despotisms' -a compliment to the Sultan -a javelin at Nicholas -in short `much ado about nothing' is all that is needed." (1851 Dec 5)
Benjamin Rush expresses his admiration for Alexander H. H. Stuart and his efforts to avoid the dissolution of the Union before the Civil War and hopes to further reconciliation between the North and South should he be elected to Congress (1874 Aug 4)
John C. Rusmisell discusses the popular election of Joseph Johnson for Governor in Virginia under the new state constitution (1851 Dec 25)
N[athan] Sargent (1794-1875), author of Public Men and Events, in several letters that reveal the turbulent condition of American politics during the period immediately preceding the Civil War, Sargent urges that articles be published in the Richmond Whig supporting his and Alexander H. H. Stuart 's positions in the upcoming elections, mentions the controversy over the Crittenden Amendment, violent feelings on both sides of the slavery issue, and urges a meeting of representatives of various Conservative groups who wish to work to preserve the Union, hopes for the defeat of John Letcher (1858-1859); and deplores the course of Goggin and Bell of Kentucky, "I can never subscribe to the doctrine that Congress must protect slavery in the Territories; never. We must repudiate that vagary." (1859 Aug 12); and discusses the effect of the outbreak at Harpers Ferry (1859 Oct 24)
R.E. Scott furnishes his views as to the nomination to be made at the Baltimore Convention (1852 May 22)
Joseph Segar writes concerning the Presidential nomination; his support for Millard Fillmore and his distaste for Scott (1852 Mar 11)
Hugh W. Sheffey compares the advantages of investing in state bonds and U.S. stock, asks his opinion of "Thompson's Revolution" before the General Assembly which means to reduce the number of circuit courts and increase the pay of judges, the House of Delegates will soon begin examining the criminal code, expects passage of the Covington and Ohio Railroad Bill, anxious that all the state internal improvements be completed so that Virginia can tap the great Western wealth, and the bill enlarging the limits of Staunton has passed (1848 Feb 12); discusses his recent attempt to pass a bill to reapportion the delegates and senators throughout the Commonwealth and Mr. Scott of Fauquier County 's proposed bill re reapportionment, failure of the bill to extend the Louisa Railroad towards Harrisonburg, his concern over the Whig nomination, "Stuart, I am satisfied that the nomination of Mr. Clay will prostrate the Whig party in the South -no young man in the South can for twenty years to come expect to rise to any post of honour or distinction if Clay should ever be elected by the Wilmot proviso vote of the North" (1848 Feb 16); the Virginia Whig Convention voted to support Zachary Taylor for the Presidential candidate (1848 Feb 25); notifies Alexander H. H. Stuart that an appropriation of six thousand dollars was made by the General Assembly to the Deaf & Dumb & Blind Institution to square its debts and warns him as its President not to come to the General Assembly for more assistance (1850 Mar 14); and writes concerning the bounty land warrant of his cousin Celly (1852 Apr 2)
W.G. [Snethen ?] asks that the Department of the Interior award land sale advertisements to the newspaper The Virginian edited by Terry and Shields (1852 Oct 9)
Lord Stirling sends a copy of The Democratic Review containing the first of a series of articles concerning his legally established rights in British North America (1852 Sep 11)
Samuel Strong writes concerning the bids for the extension of the marble work of the Capitol (1851 Nov 5)
James French Strother (1811-1860) asks Alexander H. H. Stuart to write to Mr. Hall and tell him that he believes the bill authorizing the appointment of an assistant agent will pass (1852 Jun 8)
Alexander H.H. Stuart Letters writes in great detail to Thomas Michie concerning the subjects of internal improvements, especially the James River Company, & the increase of Banking capital and the opposition of Joseph C. Cabell to their plans, and the Democratic Party being forced to accept David Campbell as Governor (1837 Jan 29); to an unknown correspondent, tries to correct the allegation by John Minor Botts that the resolution offered by Alexander H. H. Stuart at the extra session of Congress in June 1841 was copied by Alexander H. H. Stuart from Botts' resolution and presented as his own and asks for his correspondent to be a witness to what actually transpired (1845 Dec 12); furnishes a testimonial to the worthy service W.D.C. Goddard has performed in the Department of the Interior (1852 Jun 30); to his brother, Gerald B. Stuart, writes that William H. Clarke wants a barrel of his best whiskey sent, William Stuart needs a good horse, predicts big battles soon, probably at Yorktown, Harpers Ferry, or Manassas Gap, and says of the Convention, "We have a most miserable spirit prevailing in the Convention -a spirit of carping & bitter hostility to Letcher -such men as Harris, Ambler, Garnett seem disposed to assail him on every frivolous pretext" (1861 Jun 15); writes to his daughter, Maggie B. Stuart, concerning her schooling (1873 Feb 7); from the University of Virginia, to his mother, Eleanor Stuart, about his brother Archibald Stuart 's engagement (Oct 7); and to his wife, informing her that he hoped to be home from Washington soon, neither the Whig nor Democratic Parties can command the full loyalty of their followers in the present debate, and describes his anxiety about his children (n.d.)
Archibald P. Stuart assures him of his best wishes and support as he leaves for Washington and thanks him for the frock coat and the beautiful wheat (1850 Sep 29)
Eleanor Briscoe Stuart writes concerning the settling of an estate (n.d.)
J.E.B. Stuart while at West Point, answers Alexander H. H. Stuart 's questions about the annuity left him by Uncle Chapman (1851 Dec 25); and writes concerning the opportunities in real estate in Kansas where he is now serving at Fort Leavenworth (1857 Jan 28)
Oscar J.C. Stuart writes concerning Alexander H. H. Stuart 's bereavement, the genealogy of his father's family, particularly his grandfather, John Stockton, and comments on the state of Virginia politics (1859 August 8)
Isaac H. Sturgeon encloses newsclippings concerning the Labaume case (1852 Feb 4)
George William Summers (1804-1868) describes the death of their friend, Secretary of the Navy Thomas Walker Gilmer (1802-1844), who was killed by the bursting of a gun called "the Peacemaker" on board the U.S.S. Princeton on the Potomac River, near Washington, D.C. and what the loss of Secretary of State Abel P. Upshur would mean in the negotiations over the Oregon Territory with the new minister from Great Britain; feels that the quality of this Congress is decidedly inferior to the last, and his approval of Alexander H. H. Stuart 's articles in The Richmond Whig (1844 Feb 28); and comments extensively on the "farce" of the Democratic-Locofoco nomination of James Polk for President (1844 May 30)
William T. Sutherlin regrets the error of the people of Virginia at not returning Alexander H. H. Stuart to office, although he was instrumental in restoring Virginia to the Union, Alexander H. H. Stuart was not elected to public office in 1870 (1870 Nov 9); refers to the speech by William Mahone as a "campaign document" in favor of his Virginia policy and against the free Railroad Law, his desire to get rid of the obligation to build the Cumberland Gap Road and to make several other changes in the Act of Consolidation, and expresses his low opinion of Mahone and his "Radicals" (1873 Apr 4)
[J.H. Tagart ?] insists that Alexander H. H. Stuart accept his invitation to "eat a little Virginia venison with some Maryland canvass back ducks with an old friend" (1852 Nov 28)
William H. Terrill asks that Alexander H. H. Stuart exchange autographs and photographs with him (1871 Nov 17)
Lucas P. Thompson writes that various persons have urged him to suggest to Alexander H. H. Stuart that his best chance of election is to join the Know Nothing Party and run as one of their candidates but hesitates because "I entertain a prejudice not so much against the principles or what are said to be the principles of the new party as the secrecy of their organization and action" (1855 Jan 21)
Nicholas K. Trout, Senate of Virginia, addresses the re-adjustment of the public debt question with West Virginia and informs Alexander H. H. Stuart of the fate of several bills in the Legislature (1867 Jan 20)
Unidentified Letters include the following subjects: the failure to revive interest in an Act promoting a railroad from Staunton to Scottsville or the James River, the need to pursue the James River improvements, especially with the Louisa Railroad, but has little hopes of resolution until the settlement of the Bank Bill which he discusses and discusses the selection of a site for the Deaf & Dumb Asylum (1839 Mar 1); the terrible disaster on the lower Mississippi claiming the life of B.B. Stuart (1859 May 2); the editor of The Sandy Valley Advocate writes concerning the development of the great coal field in the Great Sandy Valley of Kentucky and asks what the Kentucky Whigs should do in the present political crisis (1859 Aug 27); and a Civil War letter from Bristoe Station, Virginia, where a Confederate soldier sends home fifty dollars in care of Alexander H. H. Stuart ([1861 ?] Sep 12)
Upshur County Citizens asks that Alexander H. H. Stuart come and speak to them on the issues of the day and express their support for William Leftwich Goggin (1807-1870) for Governor of Virginia (1859 Apr 6)
Thomas Walter, Architect for the Extension of the U.S. Capitol, furnishes a report on the cost of the work during the residue of fiscal year (1851 Nov 6)
Washington College Literary Society requests Alexander H. H. Stuart to give a speech before the Society on July 2nd (1857 Apr 28)
John Watt asks if Alexander H. H. Stuart will send him a copy of the appendix published in connection with his report on John Brown 's raid on Harpers Ferry, containing extracts from the personal liberty bills passed by several of the Northern states (1861 Dec 3)
Daniel Webster regrets that the information obtained in the Census Records is not particularly useful in answering Alexander H. H. Stuart 's questions about blind persons in the state of Virginia for the Virginia Institute for the Education of the Blind but suggests that an agent of the Institute might be given access to the records to compile the necessary information (1842 Aug 2); introduces Fitzhenry Warren of the General Post Office (1850 Oct 2); and regrets that the President has decided he cannot appoint Virginians to offices other than local offices (1851 Feb 8)
William J. Willey warns that "Since the action of the Convention, handing the state of Virginia over to the Confederate states, without the knowledge or consent of the people, like a lot of horses or slaves, the excitement in N.W. Virginia, is becoming most intense, and indeed, in some quarters, terrible...The clamor here for a division of the state is becoming loud and universal -I fear it will become uncontrollable" (1861 May 7)
Robert Winthrop encloses a seal, with a mistaken superscription to "Cha" Winthrop by Dr. Stuart, belonging to his great-grandfather, John Winthrop, who was a Fellow of the Royal Society, discusses family genealogy and the motto on the seal and asks him to take care of the seal while it is in his possession (1851 Apr 21); encloses a letter from Judge Thomas C. Manning (present) concerning the Mississippi Bonds question, and mentions Slater's Fund for educating the Freedmen (1882 Apr 28); regrets not seeing Alexander H. H. Stuart at the meeting of the Peabody Education Fund of which both he and Alexander H. H. Stuart were Trustees, describes the meeting and discusses politics (1884 Oct 8); discusses the death of Jefferson Davis and his opinion of the man (1889 Dec 16)
Henry Wise (1806-1876) offended at personal references in The Valley Virginian which gave a report on Alexander H. H. Stuart 's speech to the Citizens of Augusta County, at Staunton, "On the New Movement" which claimed Governor Wise had opposed the work of Alexander H. H. Stuart and had worked closely with carpet-baggers, Wise asks Alexander H. H. Stuart if he had approved the report and was it correct (1869 Feb 3); a copy of Alexander H. H. Stuart 's reply to Wise, in his speech he referred to, "parties holding the most antagonistic opinions, and having the most diverse objects in view -one party desiring the adoption of the Underwood Constitution, while the other was unalterably opposed to it -This while Governor Wells & his committee were assailing our proposition in Washington, Governor Wise & others, were attacking it at home -Thus extremes seem to meet, & the singular spectacle was presented of Gov. Wells & Gov. Wise, who probably held no other opinion in common, pulling together as it were in the same team, in opposition to the scheme" (1869 Feb 5); Wise reiterates his opposition to the "New Movement" and opposes both Governor Wells and "Negro Suffrage" (1869 Feb 8)
R.N. Wood discusses members of the American Party recently elected to Congress and fears that unless they can unify the old Whigs with the "American Organization" Millard Fillmore will not be re-elected (1856 Apr 13)
Contents List
- SERIES I: CORRESPONDENCE OF THE STUART-BALDWIN FAMILY
  - Martha S. Baldwin to Briscoe Gerard Baldwin, with his reply, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - James Barbour to Archibald Stuart, 1827 & 1831 (Box Box 1)
  - G.A. Baxter to Archibald Stuart, 1807 Sep 29 (Box Box 1)
  - Robert Beverley to Archibald Stuart, 1791-1803 (Box Box 1)
  - J.C. Breckinridge to Archibald Stuart, 1788-1815 (Box Box 1)
  - Gerald Briscoe to Archibald Stuart, 1794-1796, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Cuthbert Bullitt to Archibald Stuart, 1790 & 1823 (Box Box 1)
  - Joseph C. Cabell to Archibald Stuart, 1829 Feb 24 (Box Box 1)
  - Arthur Campbell to Archibald Stuart, 1789-1798 (Box Box 1)
  - John Coalter to Archibald Stuart, 1812 Nov 6 (Box Box 1)
  - George Davis to Archibald Stuart, 1792 Aug 17 (Box Box 1)
  - R. Gamble to Archibald Stuart, 1791-1800 (Box Box 1)
  - Hugh Holmes to Archibald Stuart, 1814-1823 (Box Box 1)
  - [Chapman] Johnson to Archibald Stuart, 1822 (Box Box 1)
  - John Lewis to [Dabney Carr ?], 1768 Jan 23 (Box Box 1)
  - John Lewis to Thomas Jefferson, 1772 Oct 4 (Box Box 1)
  - J. Marshall to Archibald Stuart, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - George Mathews to Archibald Stuart, 1791 & 1794 (Box Box 1)
  - James D. McCutchen to Joseph Janney, 1839 Mar 25 (Box Box 1)
  - Andrew Moore to Archibald Stuart, 1789-1794, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Garrett Peterson to Archibald Stuart, 1826 Jan 24 (Box Box 1)
  - William Preston to William Anderson, 1783 Jan 1 (Box Box 1)
  - [Andrew] Reid to Thomas J. Stuart, 1807 Sep 5 (Box Box 1)
  - Alexander Farish Robertson Correspondence, 1891 & 1921 (Box Box 1)
  - John Steele to Archibald Stuart, 1792 Mar 5 (Box Box 1)
  - Robert Sterritt to Joseph Janney, 837 Jul 14 (Box Box 1)
  - Eleanor (Briscoe) Stuart to Thomas J. Stuart and Margaret Briscoe, 1806-1808 (Box Box 1)
  - Martha M. Stuart to Mrs. Eleanor (Briscoe) Stuart, [n.y.] Apr 8 (Box Box 1)
  - [Charles Anderson] Wickliffe to Archibald Stuart, 1826 Feb 26 (Box Box 1)
  - William Wirt to Archibald Stuart, 1816 Aug 10 (Box Box 1)
- SERIES II: MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS OF THE STUART FAMILY
  - Architectural Drawing, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Engraving of Alexander H.H. Stuart by Danforth, Baldwin & Company (Box Box 1)
  - Financial & Legal Papers, 1792-1888 (Box Box 1)
  - Financial & Legal Papers - Accounts & Receipts, 1797-1857, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Financial & Legal Papers - Indentures (Some Copies), 1754-1836 (Box Box 1)
  - Financial & Legal Papers - Land Plats, 1770-1896, n.d. (Box Box 1)
  - Financial & Legal Papers - Legal Cases, 789-1879, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Financial & Legal Papers - Wills of Alexander Stuart, Robert Stuart, Chapman J. Stuart, & Alexander H.H. Stuart (Copies), 1812-1890 (Box Box 2)
  - Military Papers of Captain George M. Cochran, Jr., Quartermaster, 52nd Virginia Infantry, Pegram's Brigade, Early's Division, 1857, 1862-1864 (Box Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 1842-1852, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1851-1852, 1867, n.d. (Box Box 2)
  - Papers re the Settlement of Archibald Stuart's Estate, 1805-1849 (Box Box 2)
  - Speeches (Drafts) by Alexander H.H. Stuart (Box Box 2)
- SERIES III: CORRESPONDENCE OF ALEXANDER H.H. STUART
  *Unless otherwise noted the recipient of the letter is Alexander H.H. Stuart*
  - Abolitionist (Unidentified), 1841 Jun 20 (Box Box 2)
  - William H. Allen, n.y. May 13 (Box Box 2)
  - Appomattox County, Virginia, Rough & Ready Club, 1848 Sep 7 (Box Box 2)
  - Henry Carey Baird, 1859 Nov 1 (Box Box 2)
  - C.C. Baldwin, 1867 Jan 14 (Box Box 2)
  - John B. Baldwin, [1843?]-1869 (Box Box 2)
  - Joseph Baldwin, 1849-1850 (Box Box 2)
  - Joseph G. Baldwin, 1854 Sep 15 (Box Box 2)
  - I.L. Barbour, 1866 Dec 11 (Box Box 2)
  - A.W. Barton, 1850 Apr 22 (Box Box 2)
  - S.S. Baxter, 1851 Nov 24 (Box Box 2)
  - Thomas H. Benton, [ca. 1851-1853] (Box Box 2)
  - Berford & Company, 1852 Apr 12 (Box Box 2)
  - Dr. Edmund Berkeley, 1837 Jan 20 (Box Box 2)
  - James B. Bingham, 1859 Sep 28 (Box Box 2)
  - David Alexander Bokee, 1859 Oct 24 (Box Box 2)
  - Patrick Brady, 1857, 1867-1869 (Box Box 2)
  - Mary Louisa Brooks, n.y. Mar 18 (Box Box 2)
  - Alexander S. Brown, 1857-1858 (Box Box 2)
  - Joseph Rodes Buchanan, 1867 Feb 28 (Box Box 2)
  - John C. Bullitt, 1871 Oct 28 (Box Box 2)
  - William M. Burwell, 1852 Jul 23 (Box Box 2)
  - J.S. Calvert, 1868 Jan 21 (Box Box 2)
  - Samuel D. Campbell, 1830 Nov 30 (Box Box 2)
  - Lewis Cass, 1852 Jul 20 (Box Box 2)
  - John H. Cassin, 1859 Apr 13 (Box Box 2)
  - Katherine Chase, 1883 Mar 18 (Box Box 2)
  - H. Chrisman, 1855 Dec 7 (Box Box 2)
  - Bolivar Christian, 1862 Jan 18 (Box Box 2)
  - C.M. Conrad, 1855 Apr 3 (Box Box 2)
  - William Wilson Corcoran, 1885 Oct 23 (Box Box 2)
  - Thomas Corwin, 1853 Jul 10 (Box Box 2)
  - J.A. Cowardin, 1850, 1873 (Box Box 2)
  - John Jordan Crittenden, 1851 Sep 26 (Box Box 2)
  - Claudius Crozet, 1838 Jun 1 (Box Box 2)
  - Rector E.A. Dalrymple Recommendation of Thomas B. Edelin, 1852 Jul 15 (Box Box 2)
  - John W. Daniel, 1877 Jul 18 (Box Box 2)
  - J.D. Davidson, 1851-1852 (Box Box 2)
  - Garrett Davis, 1843-1851 (Box Box 2)
  - George M. Davis, 1851 Jul 27 (Box Box 2)
  - William Wallace Davis, 1851 Oct 2 (Box Box 2)
  - William Crosby Dawson, 1852 Jul 28 (Box Box)
  - Horace H. Day, 1851 Feb 7 & Mar 12 (Box Box 2)
  - Wills DeHass, 1851-1853 (Box Box 2)
  - William D. Delany, 1851-1852 (Box Box 2)
  - Charles Devens, Jr., 1852 May 24 (Box Box 2)
  - Samuel Dickson, 1867 Apr 24 (Box Box 2)
  - Dorothea Lynde Dix, [1851-1853] (Box Box 2)
  - James B. Dorman, 1852 Jun 7 (Box Box 2)
  - R.L. & John Doyle, 1851-1853 (Box Box 2)
  - G.G. Dyer, 1851 Sep 27 (Box Box 2)
  - J.L. Edwards, 1843 May 19 (& 1776 Feb 29) (Box Box 2)
  - Vespasian Ellis, 1857 Jun 10 (Box Box 2)
  - Erie Railroad Company Board of Directors, 1851 Jul 12 (Box Box 2)
  - Edward Everett, 1852-1853 (Box Box 2)
  - Charles James Faulkner, 1852 Aug 25 (Box Box 2)
  - Millard Fillmore, 1848-1854 (Box Box 2)
  - Millard Fillmore to Daniel Webster, 1851 Apr 2 (Box Box 2)
  - Edward H. Fitzhugh, 1850 Mar 25 (Box Box 2)
  - [Edward] Fontaine, 1859 Mar 25 (Box Box 2)